[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What would have happened if.?",
    "options": [
      "The bridge is broken",
      "The bridge would break",
      "The bridge had broken",
      "The bridge has been broken"
    ],
    "answer": "The bridge had broken"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Explain the meaning of 'Bring to pass'------",
    "options": [
      "cause to convince",
      "cause to carry out",
      "cause to happen",
      "cause to destroy"
    ],
    "answer": "cause to happen"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "which of the flowing sentences is the correct one?",
    "options": [
      "Paper is made of wood",
      "Paper is made by wood",
      "Paper is made on wood",
      "Paper is made from wood"
    ],
    "answer": "Paper is made from wood"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "The word bountry is closest in meaning to--",
    "options": ["sympathy", "dividing line", "familiar", "generosity"],
    "answer": "generosity"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Give the correct Passive form of-My teacher embodies all the good qualities.",
    "options": [
      "All the good qualities are embodied by my teacher",
      "All the good qualities are embodied in my teacher",
      "All the good qualities are embodied on my teacher",
      "All the good qualities are embodied to my teacher"
    ],
    "answer": "All the good qualities are embodied in my teacher"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Choose the correct indirect speech- She asked me “Are you happy in your new job?”",
    "options": [
      "She asked me if I had been happy in my new job",
      "She asked me whether I am happy in my new job",
      "She asked me if I have been happy in my new job",
      "She asked me if I was happy in my new job"
    ],
    "answer": "She asked me if I was happy in my new job"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "The meaning of the word `obese`is-",
    "options": ["Very fat", "Ugly", "Tardy", "Obnoxious"],
    "answer": "Very fat"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "A person who write about his own life writers-.",
    "options": ["a biography", "a diary", "a chronicle", "an autobiography"],
    "answer": "an autobiography"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "which of the flowing sentences is correct?",
    "options": [
      "Why you have done this?",
      "Why you had done this?",
      "Why have you done this?",
      "Why did you done this?"
    ],
    "answer": "Why have you done this?"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "what will be correct preposition to complete the sentences?“I am not good.........translation.”",
    "options": ["In", "At", "With", "About"],
    "answer": "At"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which is the noun of the word `beautiful`?",
    "options": ["Beauty", "Beautify", "Beauteous", "Most beautiful"],
    "answer": "Beauty"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "fill in the blank with the appropriate preposition: We have to go...... five minutes.",
    "options": ["In", "Beautifully", "On", "By"],
    "answer": "By"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Identify the imparative sentence.",
    "options": [
      "has been raining since morning",
      "I shall go to college.",
      "Motin is singing a song",
      "Stand up"
    ],
    "answer": "Stand up"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Fill in the gap with suitable word: To stay healthy, we must plan to have a balanced .......",
    "options": ["diet", "food", "drink", "environment"],
    "answer": "diet"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Choose the correct alternative and marks its letter on your answer sheet. The rich should not look down- the poor.",
    "options": ["upon", "towards", "for", "at"],
    "answer": "upon"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "I took a map with me,as I didn’t want to ………… my way on the journey.",
    "options": ["loose", "lose", "lost", "loss"],
    "answer": "lose"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Every driver must be held……………….. his own actions",
    "options": ["blamed for", "liable to", "responsible for", "responsible to"],
    "answer": "responsible for"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Through thick and thin---- means",
    "options": [
      "not clear in understanding",
      "under all conditions",
      "to make thick and thin",
      "of great density"
    ],
    "answer": "under all conditions"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "’Prior to’means",
    "options": ["Before", "After", "Immediately", "During the period of"],
    "answer": "Before"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Nobody knocked him down; it was an",
    "options": ["Event", "Incident", "Occurrence", "Accident"],
    "answer": "Accident"
  }
]
